Oral History Program. Administrative files. 1959-1998. UARC.0385
UCLA Library Special Collections
Oral History Program. Administrative files.
1959-1998
UCLA Library Special Collections
UARC.0385
23.6 Linear Feet (59 boxes)
Record Series 385 contains the administrative files of UCLA's Oral History Program. Files regard the Oral History Association, workshops, travel, publicity, personnel, supply, income, and other operational activities. Materials include correspondence, requests, reports, orders, budget, announcements, and ledgers.
Access
COLLECTION STORED OFF-SITE AT SRLF: Open for research. Advance notice required for access. Contact the UCLA Library Special Collections Reference Desk for paging information.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 9934669943606533
Scope and Content
Record Series 385 contains the administrative files of UCLA's Oral History Program. Files regard the Oral History Association, workshops, travel, publicity, personnel, supply, income, and other operational activities. Materials include correspondence, requests, reports, orders, budget, announcements, and ledgers.
Boxes 30-43 are pending description. No box 56 exists.
This is an active record series; additional University records are expected to be added.
- Correspondence - A to G., 1959-1970. (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Correspondence - D to L., 1961-1966. (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Correspondence - M to Z., 1960-1969. (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Correspondence., 1968-1973. (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Correspondence - outgoing., 1975-1980. (Box 2, Folder 1-6)
- Correspondence - ROHO Berkeley., 1963-1970. (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Correspondence., 1969-1979. (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Press and publicity releases., 1962-1968. (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Judge Bowron., 1962-1968. (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Photocopy requests., 1974-1978. (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Original bibliographies., 1963-1966. (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Institute manuals., n.d. (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Marc Landry University Extension. (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Oral History field collecting., Pre-1959. (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Public relations., n.d. (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Special collections., n.d. (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Supplies, expenses, and orders. (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Intra campus., n.d. (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Oral History report notes., 1961. (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Oral History bibliography., n.d. (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Oral History librarian., n.d. (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Inter library., n.d. (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Economy program book order forms., 1969. (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Japanese-American citizenship league., n.d. (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Budgets., 1961-1971. (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Budgets., 1971-1978. (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Annual reports., 1959-1974. (Box 6, Folder 2-3)
- Supplies and expenses., 1964-1972. (Box 7, Folder 1-2)
- Supplies and expenses., 1972-1980. (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Xerox and photo orders., 1978-1980. (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Berkeley., 1959-1964. (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Berkeley question., n.d. (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Objective and future needs - Galm., 1977. (Box 9, Folder 4)
- GA Times sheets., 1972-1976. (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Oral History institute., 1968. (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Oral History institute Participants Groups photograph., 1968. (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Reports., n.d. (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Oral History Institute budget., 1968. (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Budget., n.d. (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Equipment and facilities. (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Report of evaluation., n.d. (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Financial statements and membership data. (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Council minutes., n.d. (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Correspondence and forms. (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Oral History Institute applications., 1968. (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Oral History Association Colloquia., 1968-1977. (Box 11, Folder 2-3)
- Oral History Association Colloquia., 1978-1979. (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Oral History Association Newsletter., n.d. (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Oral History Association membership., n.d. (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Oral History Association Executive council memos and rosters., 1973-1979. (Box 12, Folder 4-5)
- Oral History Association Evaluation Workshop (Wingspread)., 1979. (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Workshop - Association of Recorded Sound Collections. (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Workshop - Art Librarians Society Conference., n.d. (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Workshop - Family History Symposium., n.d. (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Workshop - International Conference of Americanists (Vancouver B.C.)., n.d. (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Workshop - UCLA Panel: Oral History in California., n.d. (Box 13, Folder 6)
- UCLA Extension., n.d. (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Correspondence and announcements. (Box 13, Folder 8)
- USOE policies and procedure manual., 1967-1968. (Box 13, Folder 9)
- University Extension., 1968. (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Report on Oral History Program to Vice Chancellor Saxon (Mink)., 1970. (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Los Angeles Art Community - training session recordings., 1975-1976. (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Budget., 1983-1984. (Box 15, Folder 1-5)
- Budget., 1984-1985. (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Photocopy. (Box 16, Folder 1-3)
- Photo orders., 1980-1982. (Box 16, Folder 4-5)
- Telephone., 1980-1983. (Box 16, Folder 6-8)
- Supplies and expenses., 1981-1982. (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Corrections to published masters., 1981-1984. (Box 16, Folder 11-13)
- Xeroxing., 1977-1984. (Box 17, Folder 1-8)
- Gold Shield Budget Expenses., 1980-1982. (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Travel., 1967-1984. (Box 17, Folder 10-25)
- Travel - OHA Conference., 1982-1983. (Box 17, Folder 26)
- Travel - OHA Seattle., 1983-1984. (Box 17, Folder 27)
- Fleet Services., 1984-1985. (Box 17, Folder 28)
- ASUCLA off-campus vendors., 1984-1986. (Box 17, Folder 29-30)
- Library photographic services., 1984-1986. (Box 17, Folder 31-32)
- Book publication orders., 1984-1985. (Box 17, Folder 33)
- Storehouse., 1984-1985. (Box 17, Folder 34)
- OID photo., 1984-1987. (Box 17, Folder 35-37)
- Publications copy center., 1984-1986. (Box 18, Folder 1-2)
- Mail and messenger service., 1983-1986. (Box 18, Folder 3-5)
- Campus parking., 1985-1986. (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Faculty Center., 1985-1986. (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Telephone., 1984-1987. (Box 18, Folder 8-10)
- Miscellaneous., n.d. (Box 18, Folder 11)
- Casual payroll., 1982-1984. (Box 18, Folder 12-13)
- Casual payroll., 1984-1986. (Box 19, Folder 1-3)
- Book orders., 1963-1967. (Box 19, Folder 4-8)
- Income., 1981-1984. (Box 19, Folder 9-11)
- Caughey/Okrand account., 1982-1985. (Box 19, Folder 12-14)
- General ledger., 1985-1986. (Box 19, Folder 15)
- General ledger., 1985-1987. (Box 20, Folder 1-2)
- Detail general ledger., 1980-1982. (Box 20, Folder 3-4)
- To be recharged., 1981-1985. (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Slichter account., 1982-1985. (Box 20, Folder 6-8)
- Budget expenses - Reagan Project., 1981-1983. (Box 20, Folder 9-10)
- "Images on tape" 4 627660 5866., 1983-1984. (Box 20, Folder 11)
- Budget expenses - Maxwell account., 1981-1985. (Box 20, Folder 12-15)
- May account., 1982-1984. (Box 20, Folder 16-17)
- Medicine account fund #53273., 1982-1985. (Box 20, Folder 18-20)
- Intercollegiate Athletic funds #70500., 1983-1985. (Box 20, Folder 21-22)
- Individual record sheets., 1983-1984. (Box 20, Folder 23)
- Correspondence - general., 1981-1984. (Box 20, Folder 24)
- Telephone ledgers., 1986-1991. (Box 21, Folder 1-5)
- Miscellaneous ledger charges., 1986-1988. (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Library Reprographic Services., 1986-1991. (Box 21, Folder 7)
- United Parcel Services and Mail and Messenger Services., 1986-1991. (Box 21, Folder 8)
- Work Study., 1980-1983. (Box 21, Folder 9)
- Casual payroll., 1987-1988. (Box 22, Folder 1-3)
- Casual payroll., 1988-1989. (Box 22, Folder 4-5)
- Casual payroll., 1988-1989. (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Casual payroll., 1989-1990. (Box 23, Folder 2-3)
- Casual payroll., 1990-1991. (Box 23, Folder 4)
- UC Bindery., 1988-1991. (Box 23, Folder 5)
- General ledgers., 1986-1987. (Box 24, Folder 1-2)
- General ledgers., 1987-1988. (Box 24, Folder 3-4)
- General ledgers., 1988-1989. (Box 24, Folder 5-6)
- General ledgers., 1989-1990. (Box 25, Folder 1-2)
- General ledgers., 1990-1991. (Box 25, Folder 3-4)
- Income orders., 1983-1987. (Box 25, Folder 5-7)
- Income orders., 1987-1989. (Box 26, Folder 1-2)
- OID photo., 1986-1989. (Box 26, Folder 3-4)
- Fleet Services., 1986-1989. (Box 26, Folder 5-7)
- Fleet Services., 1990. (Box 27, Folder 1)
- Miscellaneous accounting., 1984-1989. (Box 27, Folder 2)
- Copy Center., 1988-1991. (Box 27, Folder 3-5)
- Furniture requests and typewriters., 1987-1989. (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Keys and reprographic services., 1984-1991. (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Budget documents., 1986-1990. (Box 28, Folder 1-4)
- Casual timesheets., 1991. (Box 28, Folder 5)
- Bookbindery orders, memos, and procedures., 1987-1990. (Box 28, Folder 6)
- OID Audio Visual Services, audiotape orders, and audio visual equipment., 1985-1990. (Box 28, Folder 7)
- Los Angeles Department of Water and Power., 1985-1987. (Box 28, Folder 8)
- Museum of Cultural History and Anderson Graduate School of Management., 1983-1989. (Box 28, Folder 9)
- Pasadena Art Alliance., 1987-1990. (Box 28, Folder 10)
- Los Angeles Olympic Organizing Committee (LAOOC) and UCLA School of Law., 1985. (Box 28, Folder 11)
- Campus Facilities and Maintenance, Dictaphone., 1983-1989. (Box 28, Folder 12)
- Faculty Center, Federal Express., 1980-1990. (Box 28, Folder 13)
- Faculty Advisory Committee minutes., 1958-1989. (Box 29, Folder 1-2)
- Extramural projects., 1987. (Box 29, Folder 3)
- Category listing and prospective interviewees., 1986-1989. (Box 29, Folder 4-5)
- Faculty Advisory Committee correspondence., 1959-1989. (Box 29, Folder 6-8)
- Faculty Advisory Committee minutes., 1990. (Box 29, Folder 9)
- Research Notes, Water for Los Angeles, Mona Osborne, Gerald W. Jones, Robert Lee and Samuel B. Nelson, 4 folders (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Research Notes, Water for Los Angeles, Alfred Driscoll, Robert V. Phillips, Gerard Wyss., n.d.; 3 folders (Box 31)
- Research Notes, Norman Cousins., n.d.; 7 folders (Box 32)
- Research Notes, George Gregory., n.d.; 6 folders (Box 33)
- Tape History Cards., n.d.; 5 folders (Box 34)
- Research materials, Los Angeles Olympic Organizing Committee., n.d.; 1 folders (Box 35)
- Bibliographic Instruction, Expenses and General Ledgers - Fleet services, Office of Instructional Development, Office supplies, Postage, Telephone, Transcript correspondence and income - Leave Accruals., c. 1985-1993 (Box 35, Box 36, Box 37, Box 38, Box 39, Box 40, Box 41)
- Correspondence of Doyce Nunis and Elizabeth Dixon - A-L., c.1959-1965 (Box 42)
- Correspondence of Doyce Nunis and Elizabeth Dixon - M-Z., c. 1959-1964 (Box 43)
- General ledgers., 1989-1995; 3 folders (Box 44)
- Audio Visual., 1990-1995. (Box 45, Folder 1)
- Leave Accrual Benefit Reports., 1988-1990. (Box 45, Folder 2)
- Ledgers., 1997 Apr-Jun. (Box 45, Folder 3)
- Ledgers., 1996 Nov-1997 Mar. (Box 45, Folder 4)
- Ledgers., 1996 Jul-Oct. (Box 46, Folder 1)
- Ledgers., 1996 Jun 30. (Box 46, Folder 2)
- Wilshire at Westwood Hines Interest., 1993-1996. (Box 46, Folder 3-6)
- Advice and Assistance., 1983-1990. (Box 46, Folder 7)
- Advice and Assistance., 1991-1995. (Box 47, Folder 1)
- Bibl. Inst., 1983-1990. (Box 47, Folder 2)
- Information Requests., 1972-1989. (Box 47, Folder 3)
- Library Facilities., 1983-1990. (Box 47, Folder 4)
- Insurance., 1976-1993. (Box 47, Folder 5)
- Publicity., 1989-1991. (Box 48, Folder 1)
- Publicity., 1986-1988. (Box 48, Folder 2)
- Publicity., 1986-1989. (Box 48, Folder 3)
- Publicity., 1966-1985. (Box 48, Folder 4)
- Publicity., To 1985. (Box 48, Folder 5)
- Word Processing., 1982-1985. (Box 48, Folder 6)
- Personnel Consultant Agreements., 1981-1984. (Box 48, Folder 7)
- 1993 Mar-Dec. (Box 49, Folder 1)
- 1994 Jul-Dec. (Box 49, Folder 2)
- 1992 Oct-1993 Jan. (Box 49, Folder 3)
- Emergency Procedures. (Box 50, Folder 1)
- Personnel (Searches)., 1984-1995. (Box 50, Folder 2)
- Personnel (Miscellaneous). (Box 50, Folder 3)
- Personnel (Upward Bound). (Box 50, Folder 4)
- Personnel (Memoranda)., 1977-1993. (Box 50, Folder 5)
- Personnel (Job Postings)., 1983-1993. (Box 50, Folder 6)
- Personnel (Job Descriptions/Postings)., 1977-1985. (Box 50, Folder 7)
- Personnel (Research Asst.)., 1988-1994. (Box 50, Folder 8)
- Detail General Ledger., 1992 Jul 31. (Box 51, Folder 1)
- Detail General Ledger., 1993 Jul 31. (Box 51, Folder 2)
- Supply Orders., 1991-1994. (Box 51, Folder 3-4)
- Assistant I., 1996 Feb. (Box 52, Folder 1)
- Audit Edit Log Sheets., 1986-1987. (Box 52, Folder 2)
- Transcriber Log Sheets., 1986-1987. (Box 52, Folder 3)
- Budget Detail., 1992-1993. (Box 52, Folder 4)
- Income Orders., 1993-1994. (Box 53, Folder 1-4)
- Supply Orders., 1986-1990. (Box 53, Folder 5-6)
- Income Orders., 1992. (Box 53, Folder 7)
- Income Orders., 1987-1992. (Box 54, Folder 1-7)
- Supply Orders., 1990-1991. (Box 54, Folder 8)
- Copy Center Orders., 1992-1993. (Box 55, Folder 1)
- Copy Center Forms., 1995. (Box 55, Folder 2)
- Off Campus Forms., 1996-1998. (Box 55, Folder 3)
- NBI to PC Conversion., 1994-1996. (Box 55, Folder 4)
- Workstudy., 1995. (Box 55, Folder 5)
- Budget Cut., 1990-1993. (Box 55, Folder 6-7)
- Personnel (Searches)., 1983-1996. (Box 57, Folder 1)
- Personnel(Bindey Assistant Search)., 1987. (Box 57, Folder 2)
- Personnel (Memos). (Box 57, Folder 3)
- OHP Internships., 1973-1981. (Box 57, Folder 4)
- Word Processing., 1982-1985. (Box 57, Folder 5)
- Personnel (Serves Description)., 1968-1981. (Box 57, Folder 6)
- Personnel (Affirmative Action)., 1974-1985. (Box 57, Folder 7)
- Personnel (Prospective Interviewers)., 1987-1993. (Box 57, Folder 8)
- Personnel General Ledger. (Box 58)
- Personnel General Ledger. (Box 59)
- Computers., 1992-1993. (Box 59, Folder 1)
- Budget Detail., 1991-1992. (Box 59, Folder 2)
- Budget Detail., 1994-1995. (Box 59, Folder 3)
- Travel., 1984-1991. (Box 59, Folder 4)